<world>
    <room name="Dojo" keyword="Dojo">
        <desc>You are entering the Dojo, it has stood on this mountain for hundreds of years. To the south you can see the Nanfang Village, but you might find something else if you go down.</desc>
        <item name="nunchucks" damage="90" speed="28">
            <desc>Wooden sticks on a chain. Don't hit yourself though.</desc>
        </item>
        <item name="meditation stick" damage="50" speed="18">
            <desc>Wooden stick (no chain), works as a meditation aid.</desc>
        </item>
        <exits>-1,Village,-1,-1,-1,Underground</exits>
    </room>
    <room name="Underground" keyword="Underground">
        <desc>You are now entering a secret passage to an unknown world, not yet opened. You can only go back the way you came in from.</desc>
        <item name="candle" damage="20" speed="10">
            <desc>An old, barely working candle. It does not come with matches.</desc>
        </item>
        <exits>-1,-1,-1,-1,Dojo,-1</exits>
    </room>
    <room name="Nanfang Village" keyword="Village">
        <desc>You are now entering the Nanfang Village, one full of lively night markets and too many people. If you look north to the mountains you'll see the Dojo, to the east lies the Red Lake, and to the south a lovely poet's house.</desc>
        <item name="hat" damage="10" speed="5">
            <desc>Something to shield you from the sun.</desc>
        </item>
        <item name="grilled corn" damage="10" speed="10">
            <desc>One of the villagers' favorite street food.</desc>
        </item>
        <exits>Dojo,House,-1,Lake,-1,-1</exits>
    </room>
    <room name="Red Lake" keyword="Lake">
        <desc>You are now entering the vast forest surrounding the Red Lake. The lake gets its name from the vibrant mushrooms that grow all along the bottom of it, painting the water a bloody red color. But be careful, they're poisonous. To the east lies the Nanfang Village, you can almost smell the tasty food. Go south and you'll be surrounded by bamboo taller than the oldest trees.</desc>
        <item name="mushrooms" damage="15" speed="10">
            <desc>Good source of flavor for your enemy's soup.</desc>
        </item>
        <exits>-1,Forest,Village,-1,-1,-1</exits>
    </room>
        <room name="Bamboo Forest" keyword="Forest">
        <desc>You are now entering the Bamboo Forest, there are so many trees it is hard to see ahead of you. Luckily, there's narrow path that was carved hundreds of years ago. Don't stray too far or you'll get lost. To the north lies the Red Lake, but look east and you'll see the beginnings of the poet's garden.</desc>
        <item name="dagger" damage="60" speed="25">
            <desc>A small but handy item, with a hilt carved out of bamboo.</desc>
        </item>
        <exits>Lake,-1,House,-1,-1,-1</exits>
    </room>
        <room name="Matsuo's Tea House" keyword="House">
        <desc>You are now entering Matsuo's Tea House, the place is run by an old, retired poet. He also takes care of the lush, green gardens that create a path to the entrance of the house. If you look west, you'll find bamboo towering over trees, but look north and you'll see the markets that await you in the Nanfang Village.</desc>
        <item name="tea pot" damage="50" speed="19">
            <desc>For brewing your favorite drinks, made of clay.</desc>
        </item>
        <item name="calligraphy brush" damage="20" speed="22">
            <desc>An artist's favorite weapon of choice.</desc>
        </item>
        <exits>Village,-1,-1,Forest,-1,-1</exits>
    </room>
</world>